<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>WaxaM</title>
    <link>https://waxam.io/rss.xml</link>
    <description>WaxaM llc</description>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2020 https://waxam.io</copyright>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 14:47:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://waxam.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Integrations</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/integrations</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <p>Waxam can integrate products and sevices no matter where you are thanks to our waxam CDN.</p>
 ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/integrations</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 19:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web components</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/web-components</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <p>WaxaM works commonly in the following web component languages and are recognized industry leaders in the development and trainings associated with</p>
<ul><li>LitElement</li>
<li>VanillaJS</li>
<li>OpenWC workflows and tooling</li>
</ul>
<p><span>Know how to make web components but unsure of the best way to deploy? Talk to our team about our recommendations around how to ship web components for maximal resuse!</span></p>
<img src="files/overflow.png" alt="dfgdfgdfgdfg" height="100"/> ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/web-components</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/services</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <p>Waxam provides all your training needs for your web component future</p>
<h2 id="header-3233e840-1cd4-9024-cc31-dbcf09a0ad1a">CDN</h2>
<p>Know that web components are the future but just want a place that hosts them and quickly? WaxaM specializes in getting the build and development piece out of the way for one low price. Just click through our CDN creation page, put in your payment details and hit go. In 30 seconds you'll have assets you can use anywhere all over the globe with a single line of javascript in order to plug it into your products.</p>
<h2 id="header-01f11a19-6817-b737-edf3-45554d131d0d">Hosting</h2>
<p>Love HAX but don't love hosting? Us too. That's why we built the WaxaM hosting, a zero config, click and build platfor that allows you to rapidly get yourself online.</p>
<ul><li>Content is up on our CDN instantly</li>
<li>Assets are made using web components. Want to break up with us in a year? Take your stuff with you and it'll all still work (try that with Wix)</li>
<li>One low monthly or yearly price</li>
</ul>
<p><span>Consulting services</span></p>
<p><span>Want access to our team's brains but not through these product offerings? Let's talk!</span></p>
<p></p>
 ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/services</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAXEditor</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/haxeditor</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <p>HAXeditor is a revolutionary new way of editing content. It's a block editor that can be extended by simply extending the web.</p>
<p>Waxam experts can help you...</p>
<ul><li>Implement HAXEditor in your organization</li>
<li>Create new elements for the HAXeditor</li>

<li>Teach you how to make the most of your web development with Web components that work in HAXeditor</li>
</ul>
 ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/haxeditor</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAXcms</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/haxcms</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <p>HAXcms is a distributed publishing solution that requires minimal backend to setup and then no backend to power published sites.</p>
<p>This workflow makes it ridiculously fast and secure without compromising on features.</p>
<p>WaxaM are experts in implementation, integration, extending and making recommendations about the HAXcms platform</p>
<p>What we can provide</p>
<ul><li>Implementation optimizations</li>

<li>Trainings on using and building themes for HAXcms</li>
<li>Best practices</li>
</ul>
 ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/haxcms</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Waxam</title>
      <link>https://waxam.io/item-b5040654-1cde-4f9b-9856-874ec676c1a5</link>
      <description>
          <![CDATA[ <img style="width: 25%; margin: 0px auto; display: block;" src="files/bee.png" alt="WaxaM - Your a busy bee, let us deal with the hive, you deal with the honey." dataeditable="" datahaxray="Image"/><h2 id="header-3c4925f7-adb7-3928-48d7-ba4a1c410bf9">WaxaM</h2>
<p>We're here to flip the industry on its head. Forward, backward, upside-down; WaxaM is built to survive any sea change.</p>
<p><i>Boldness</i>
 or <i>blindness</i>
 in that statement?</p>
<p>We're here to build a platform that enhances the open web and makes it fundamentally more sustainable, leveraging the web components standard.</p>
<p>We're here to empower authors, bloggers, developers, anyone involved in the web to deliver a faster, more accessible, and fundamentally better product.</p>
<p>Do you care about the open web?</p>
<p>Do you want to eliminate platform lock in?</p>
<p>Do you want to build website without having to think about it so much?</p>
<p>Do you care about permanence, portability, and data privacy?</p>
<p>Then we're building a platform and solutions for you. Built on top of the power open source projects HAXiam, HAXcms and HAXeditor, Waxam is your one stop for all things training and support related in the HAX ecosystem. Our experts live sleep and breath HAX related solutions and we can help you get started today.</p>
<p>contact: info@waxam.io</p>
<hero-banner title="Waxam" image="files/IMG_20181228_113330.jpg" details="Web components based SaaS, hosting, training and support services" button-text="More coming soon!" button-link="services" accent-color="grey" style="width: 100%;" __utils="[object HTMLElement]"></hero-banner>
 ]]>
      </description>
      <category></category>
      <guid>https://waxam.io/item-b5040654-1cde-4f9b-9856-874ec676c1a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>